As you begin this course you must be wondering,
在你开始学习这门课之前 你可能会想
what exactly will be covered in this course?
我到底会学到哪些内容呢？
I am now going to explain to you exactly what we are going to deal with
接下来我就会告诉你我们将会学习到的东西
in this course, and how it is positioned in the bigger scheme of things
以及它在全栈开发这个大蓝图中
in this full stack web development specialization.
的大致定位
Going back to our picture of the full stack web development specialization,
让我们看回这张介绍我们这个全栈 web 开发 专项课程的概述图
we are now still dealing with the front end development.
我们现在关心的是前端开发部分
And in particular, in this course,
特别地 在这节课里
we're gonna concentrate on the UI framework, which is bootstrap.
我们将会着重学习 Bootstrap
So in this scheme, this is the module dealing with the bootstrap
这个在前端的界面框架
on the front-end side, the presentation layer side.
它同时也是表示层
In this course, we are going to cover bootstrap in a lot of detail.
事实上 我们将会学习到大量有关 Bootstrap 的细节
We'll also introduce you to web tools,
我们还会学习如何使用一些 web 工具
in particular Node.js and NPM, and Bower.
比如说 Node.js, NPM 和 Bower
The remaining web tools we will see in the next course.
对于其它的 web 工具 我们将在下一门课中介绍
This course itself, is organized into four modules,
对于这门课而言 我们一共有四个单元
each module corresponding to one week of work.
每一个单元对应着一周的学习量
In the first module we'll give you the big picture view of
在第一个单元里 我们将会了解到 全栈 web 开发的大蓝图
Full Stack Web Development, then we'll introduce you to Bootstrap.
然后我们会向你简要地介绍一下 Bootstrap
Then we'll talk about the responsive web design, and the Bootstrap grid system.
接着 我们会谈谈响应式网页设计和 Bootstrap 中的网格系统
We'll also look at an important component in Bootstrap, which is the navigation bar.
我们还会谈到如何 Bootstrap 的导航栏
And at the end of this module, you will have your first assignment.
然后在本单元的最后 你需要完成一个大作业
As you go through this course, you will be building up a website to help you to
在你完成这整门课的同时 你将会通过 你在课中亲自搭建的网站
consolidate all the knowledge that you are acquiring in this course.
来将所有你在这门课中学习到的东西 整合在一起
In the second module we will be dealing with Bootstrap's CSS components.
而在第二个单元里 我们将会学习一些 Bootstrap 的 CSS 组件
These components are pure CSS components,
这些组件都是纯粹的 CSS 组件
which means that they don't need JavaScript for them to work.
这意味着它们不需要 JavaScript 就可以工作
In particular, we'll look at user input components, like buttons and forms.
特别地 我们将会学习到一些用户输入类的组件 比如按钮和表格
Then we'll look at displaying content, using tables, panels and wells.
然后我们会学习如何用表格 面板和 well 来漂亮地显示内容
Then we'll move on to image and media, dealing with images,
接着我们会学习图片和多媒体 并学习 如何在我们的网页中
thumbnails and media objects that are included in your webpage.
使用图片 缩略图和多媒体对象
Then we'll look at alerting users by using things like labels,
我们还会学习到如何通过标签 徽章和进度条
badges, alerts and progress bars.
来提醒或警告用户
At the end of the second module you'll have the second assignment 2.
而在第二单元的最后 你则需要完成 第 2 个大作业
The third module deals
而在第三个单元里 我们会专门学习
exclusively with Bootstrap's JavaScript supported components.
Bootstrap 中支持的 JavaScript 组件
So we'll look at the overview of Bootstrap's JavaScript components, and
我们会先大概看一下 Bootstrap 有哪些 JavaScript 组件
we'll explore tabs, pills, and tabbed navigation.
然后我们会学习标签页, 胶囊式标签页和页签导航
Then we'll look at collapse, accordion, ScrollSpy, and Affix.
接着我们会学习折叠
Then, we look at Tooltips, Popovers and Modals.
我们还会学习到工具提示 弹出框和模态框
This pretty much covers all the JavaScript components.
而上面说的这些其实就已经涵盖了大部分的 JavaScript 组件了
We'll also look at Carousel as an important component there.
我们也会学习到轮播这个重要的组件
At the end of this module, we'll have assignment 3 due.
而在第 3 单元的最后 你同样需要完成一个大作业
The final module rounds out our discussion on bootstrap JavaScript competence,
在最后一个单元里 我们将会学习一点 关于 jQuery 的知识
by dealing with Bootstrap and jQuery, and how they work together.
并学习如何使用 jQuery 中一些对应的 JavaScript 方法
And we'll also see how Bootstrap's JavaScript competence can be controlled
来控制 Bootstrap 中对应的
through the JavaScript methods that are available for this competence.
JavaScript 组件
Then we'll look at Node.js and Node Package Manager.
接着我们会稍微学习一点 Node.js 和 NPM 的知识
We'll also look at CSS preprocessors, Less and Sass.
并学习 Less 和 Sass 这两款 CSS 预处理器 的一些知识
Then we'll encounter our first web tool, which is Bower.
然后我们将会学习到我们接触的 第一个 web 工具 Bower
At the end of this module, you'll have assignment 4.
而在第 4 单元的最后 同样的 你需要完成一个大作业
This completes this course.
以上 就是这一门课的大概内容
I hope you have a good time going through this course and
我希望你能很开心地学习这门课
take the maximum benefit out of learning the material in this course.
并能够从这门课提供的材料中收获良多
This course will set up the foundation upon
相信这门课会给你打下
which we'll build in the following courses.
一个坚实的基础 【翻译 - Carefree0910】